kpcb.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy | Kleiner Perkins

Effective Date: August 15th, 2016 

## YOUR PRIVACY MATTERS

Thank you for visiting kleinerperkins.com and/or [fellows.kleinerperkins.com](http://fellows.kleinerperkins.com/) (each, as applicable, the "Site"), which is owned and operated by Kleiner Perkins Caufield & Byers ("KPCB"). **By using or accessing the Site in any way, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent to our collection, use and sharing of your information in the manner described herein.**

KPCB is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully in order to understand what information KPCB collects about visitors to the Site, and how KPCB uses that information. If you do not agree with the content of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site. We encourage you to check our Site frequently to see the current Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions of Use in effect and any changes that may have been made to them. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by posting the revised Privacy Policy and the revised effective date on this Site, by sending you an e-mail, and/or by some other means. Please note that if you’ve opted not to receive legal notice emails from us (or you haven’t provided us with your email address), those legal notices will still govern your use of the Site, and you are still responsible for reading and understanding them. If you use the Site after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been posted, this means you agree to all of the changes. This Policy is part of our Terms and Conditions of Use. Please click here to see that agreement. 

This Privacy Policy only covers our treatment of your personal information that we gather when you are accessing or using our Site, but not to the practices of companies we don’t own or control, or people that we don’t manage.

## TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED BY KPCB

KPCB collects two types of information from visitors to the Site, non-personal information and personal information. Non-personal information is information that does not, by itself, identify the visitor as a specific individual. Personal information, is information that specifically identifies a visitor to the Site, or which includes contact information. If you sign up to receive KPCB newsletters, provide contact information or other information about yourself when signing up for a KPCB event, or express interest in the KPCB Fellows Program, KPCB may request and you may be required to provide personal information, including, without limitation, your e-mail address. By providing KPCB with personal information via the Site, you expressly agree to its collection and use as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not want to receive communications from us, please indicate your preference by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of an email message. You may obtain access to your personal information collected by KPCB by sending an e-mail to [privacy@kpcb.com](mailto:privacy@kpcb.com).

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

Visitors may access the Site while remaining anonymous and without revealing any personal information. KPCB may collect information during your visit to the Site through our automatic data collection tools, which may include cookies and other commonly used information-gathering tools. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the website from which you arrived at a KPCB website. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address and clickstream behavior (i.e. the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with KPCB websites).

A "cookie" is a small piece of data stored on a user's browser, and contains non-personally identifiable information about the user. When you visit the website, KPCB may place a "cookie" in order to improve your experience by recognizing you when you visit the website and in order to allow the company to optimize the information presented based on your demonstrated areas of interest. Cookies may also be used to compile information about website usage. If you subsequently provide us with personal information such as your email address, we will associate any cookies on your browser with that information such that you will no longer be an anonymous visitor to the site.

Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites. Our Site does not support Do Not Track requests at this time, which means that we collect information about your online activity both while you are on the Site and after you leave our Site.

## CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

KPCB is committed to protecting the privacy of young children, and therefore does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Site from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under the age of 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE SITE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. In the event that KPCB discovers that personal information has been collected from a person under 13 years of age, without verified parental consent in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), KPCB will delete such information.

## HOW KPCB USES AND SHARES INFORMATION

KPCB may use personal information you provide in order to contact you. For example, if you sign up for the KPCB newsletter, KPCB may use your contact information to send you the KPCB newsletter and other communications from KPCB. If you provide KPCB with contact information or other information about yourself in connection with a KPCB event, KPCB may use that information internally and to communicate with you regarding KPCB’s events. Because KPCB is committed to protecting your privacy, KPCB will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose this information to any third party, except as described in this Privacy Policy. Personal information may be disclosed under the limited circumstances described below, and you agree that KPCB may do so by submitting your personal information. By providing any personal information to the Site, all users, including without limitation users in the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States. KPCB may share non-personal information from which individuals cannot be identified, and which do not relate to individuals in aggregate form, with third parties for business purposes, such as consultants and advisors to the company. KPCB will disclose your personal information to a third party if required to do so by law or if, in good faith, KPCB believes that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend KPCB's rights and property or prevent fraud; (3) protect KPCB against abuse, misuse or unauthorized use of KPCB's products or services; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of its personnel, users of this Site or the public. The servers that serve the Site automatically identify a computer by its IP address. If KPCB, in good faith, determines that you have used the service to menace, threaten, harass, intimidate or otherwise deceptively pose as another person, your actions will be investigated and your IP address may be disclosed to the recipient of any email, their legal counsel or representatives, and law enforcement officials as part of such an investigation. KPCB may transfer its database, including personal information contained therein, to a third party who acquires all or substantially all of the assets or stock of KPCB whether by merger, acquisition, reorganization or otherwise.

If you submit unsolicited business plan ideas or slide decks to KPCB through the Site, KPCB cannot and will not accept responsibility for protecting against misuse or disclosure of any confidential or proprietary information included in such materials, in the absence of KPCB’s express written agreement to do so. Except as expressly set forth in this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, any plans, information and other materials you submit in connection with this Site may be used or disclosed by KPCB for any purpose and in any manner, as KPCB determines in its sole discretion. Please consider this carefully before sending KPCB any information or other materials that you deem confidential or proprietary.

## INFORMATION SUBMITTED BY CURRENT OR PROSPECTIVE KPCB FELLOWS

If you submit information about yourself, such as your name, contact information, resumé, and other application materials, through the KPCB Fellows website at [fellows.kleinerperkins.com](http://fellows.kleinerperkins.com/), KPCB may use such information internally in connection with the KPCB Fellows program. Additionally, KPCB may share such information with its portfolio companies so that such companies may review your materials and contact you in connection with the KPCB Fellows program. Be aware that KPCB does not control the portfolio companies’ actions with respect to such information, and assumes no responsibility for how the portfolio companies use the information KPCB provides to them in connection with the KPCB Fellows program. KPCB will not share such information with any other third parties, except as specified in this Privacy Policy. 

## LINKED WEBSITES

This Site (including, without limitation, such features as KPCB’s newsletters) may contain links or otherwise provide access to third party websites and services. Please be aware that KPCB has no control over the policies and practices of third party websites or businesses as to privacy or anything else and is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. KPCB encourages users to be aware when they leave this Site and to read the privacy statements of each website they visit that collects personal information. While KPCB carefully chooses the websites to link to, this Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on this Site.
